var myQuestions = [

	{

		question: "What does PHP stand for?<br>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;i) Personal Home Page<br>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;ii) Hypertext Preprocessor<br>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;iii) Pretext Hypertext Processor<br>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;iv) Preprocessor Home Page",

		answers: {

			a: 'Both i) and iii)',

			b: 'Both ii) and iv)',

			c: 'Only ii)',

                        d: 'Both i) and ii)'

		},

		correctAnswer: 'd'

	},

	{

		question: "The filesize() function returns the file size in _____",

		answers: {

			a: ' bits',

			b: 'bytes',

			c: 'kilobytes',

                        d: 'gigabytes'

		},

		correctAnswer: 'b'
	},

{

		question: "How should we add a single line comment in our PHP code? <br>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;i) /?<br>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;ii) //<br>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;iii) #<br>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;iv) /* */",

		answers: {

		    a: ' Only ii)',

			b: 'i), iii) and iv)',

			c: 'ii), iii) and iv)',

                        d: 'Both ii) and iv)'

		},

		correctAnswer: 'c'

	},
{

		question: "Which of the following PHP statement/statements will store 111 in variable num?<br>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;i) int $num = 111;<br>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;ii) int mum = 111;<br>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;iii) $num = 111;<br>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;iv) 111 = $num;",

		answers: {

			a: 'Both i) and ii)',

			b: 'i), ii), iii) and iv)',

			c: 'Only iii)',

                        d: 'Only i)'

		},

		correctAnswer: 'c'

	},
{

		question: "Which statement will output $x on the screen?",

		answers: {

			a: 'echo "\$x;"',

			b: 'echo "$x;"',

			c: 'echo "/$$x;"',

            d: 'echo "$x;";'

		},

		correctAnswer: 'a'

	},
{

		question: "Which one of the following function is capable of reading a specific number of characters from a file?",

		answers: {

			a: 'fgets()',

			b: 'fget()',

			c: 'fileget()',

                        d: 'filegets()'

		},

		correctAnswer: 'a'

	},
{

		question: "Which of the following PHP function will return true if a variable is an array or false if it is not an array?",

		answers: {

			a: 'this_array()',

			b: 'is_array()',

			c: 'do_array()',

                        d: 'in_array()'

		},

		correctAnswer: 'b'

	},
{

		question: "A function in PHP which starts with _ (double underscore) is known as _____",

		answers: {

			a: 'Magic Function',

			b: 'Inbuilt Function',

			c: 'Default Function',

                        d: 'User Defined Function'

		},

		correctAnswer: 'a'

	},
{

		question: "How to define a function in PHP?",

		answers: {

			a: 'function {function body}',

			b: 'data type functionName(parameters) {function body}',

			c: 'functionName(parameters) {function body}',

                        d: 'function functionName(parameters) {function body}'

		},

		correctAnswer: 'd'

	},
{

		question: "If a = 12 what will be returned when (a == 12) ? 5 : 1 is executed?",

		answers: {

			a: '12',

			b: '1',

			c: 'Error',

                        d: '5'

		},

		correctAnswer: 'd'

	}
]